(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
SOLD OUT ON YOU
Are you kidding me?
I'll give you one each day.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Ms. Dam.
Let's meet every day.
DEOKCHEON REST AREA
I mean, why would I…
receive my meds from you?
Our materials make up 90%
of L'Étoile's La Fin Essence.
That means
90% of Gojeuneok Bio's fate
depends on L'Étoile's product launch.
I can't let
the home shopping host's condition risk
such an important broadcast.
Wait, hold on.
Did you just say "broadcast"?
Wait…
HOME SHOPPING BROADCAST
PARTNERSHIP AGREEMENT
"As L'Étoile's La Fin Essence
will be launched through a live broadcast,
the parties under this agreement
are obligated
to maintain and manage
the home shopping host's condition."
"If any action is required, both parties
must work together to resolve the matter."
Yes. One pack per day.
That's the condition I'm requesting
for our contract renewal.
Then…
this means you're going to
supply the raw material?
Yes, if both you and L'Étoile
accept my condition.
Of course, we will!
Of course!
You can't take it back.
Then, I'll see you tomorrow.
Wait!
Well…
You still need to take care
of the current problem.
It's all resolved now, right?
Yes.
Oh, right.
I can take a cab, so don't worry.
You can head home now.
Take care.
Wait!
I…
187-2 SEONGCHO-DONG
DEOKCHEON REST AREA
TO 187-2 SEONGCHO-DONG
ESTIMATED TIME
2 HOURS 20 MINUTES
Still, there's no traffic at this hour,
so it won't take long.
It's not very close though.
My nickname is "Dam Talk," you know.
A couple hours will just fly by
if you're with me.
My regular viewers even wait
until just before products sell out
so I won't end the show early.
Let's just go quietly.
But that's not polite.
I can't just sit by
while you drive long distance.
I'd appreciate that.
That would be more helpful.
All right.
Just in case you might be thinking
that I can sleep well
without my pills,
I'm just keeping my eyes closed.
I'm blocking out visual stimuli
to trick my brain
into thinking I'm sleeping.
You might actually sleep
if you don't talk.
Geez, you're being quite harsh
to someone with insomnia.
You heard that?
How long have you been
taking sleeping pills for?
It seems like it's been a long time.
How would you know that?
How did you know
that I've been taking them
for a long time?
I majored in chemistry.
No wonder why.
I knew you weren't the humanities type.
Then, what's the STEM type like?
The type who points out every detail.
I can hardly say anything around you.
Those pills suppress
the central nervous system,
so you need to be careful
with long-term use.
Are you showing off your expertise?
Ms. Dam, the side effects
aren't something to take lightly either.
Hallucinations, sleepwalking, and--
I don't think there was a clause
allowing you to nag me.
Give it. I'll add it then.
No, we already made the deal,
so it's over.
-Let me just add it.
-Don't be so cheap.
-Give it to me.
-Focus on driving.
Just kidding.
We're here.
Ms. Dam.
Ms. Dam--
What?
We're here.
I wasn't asleep.
-Yes, you were.
-No, I wasn't.
-I said you were.
-I said I wasn't asleep.
You called my name like…
-four times.
-It was three times. Get out.
Oh, right. We…
We should exchange numbers
if we're going to meet
every day until the show.
There's no need for that.
Let's pick a set time and place instead.
AUGUST
As you can see, I have no idea
where I'll be at any time.
I won't contact you for any other reasons,
so just give me your number.
Okay?
Goodness, thank you so much.
Could you open the door?
-It's open.
-It is?
You're right.
But why isn't it working?
It's not opening.
Why are you so impatient?
It opens if you push slowly.
Get home safe then.
Gosh, he startled me.
MATTHEW
MR. MECHOORI
BORN AND RAISED IN DEOKPUNG
GOOD MORNING
HAVE A GREAT DAY
What on earth?
HAPPINESS COMES WITH THE RAIN
I didn't think he'd be like this at all.
This is awful.
Oh, right!
Sung-mi.
How long have you been out here?
You little…
Where the hell have you been?
For crying out loud.
Have you lost your mind?
You think whatever I say
is a joke, don't you?
I clearly told you earlier
to go home
and not do anything else but rest.
I was going to give you some porridge,
but you weren't home and wouldn't pick up!
Where on earth did you go?
Why are you making such a fuss?
I was away for just a few hours…
I'm worried you'll burn out.
Hey. They say even phones
are at their strongest
when their batteries are at ten percent.
Just like you!
Sung-mi.
Aren't you curious about who I met--
No, I'm not.
I'm sleeping over tonight.
-What?
-We'll go to work together tomorrow.
It was my fault for leaving you alone.
I'm the one to blame.
I'm totally fine though.
Shut up!
Yes, ma'am.
Sung-mi.
I experienced something really strange.
Don't you have any upbeat music?
This is music that helps plants relax.
Is this a dentist's office or what?
I felt relaxed.
Was it because of the music?
Or…
Ms. Dam.
Let's meet every day.
I must be out of my mind.
I must be crazy.
GOJEUNEOK BIO
-Oh, my gosh!
Where are you right now?
You…
Hey.
Do you still have dreams
about the military?
Was it a full night's rest?
You're still not awake.
Company, attention!
I'm heading out.
Hey, stay a bit longer.
Let me feed you something.
How about a fancy restaurant?
Hold on…
Renewal?
L'ÉTOILE
ERIC SEO
You're renewing the contract?
-Are you up now?
-Yeah.
-Let me use some of your lotion.
-Sure.
-Sung-mi.
-Yeah?
How was I during the night?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean…
Did I…
toss and turn
or talk in my sleep?
Or did I walk around or anything?
You slept like a log.
Right?
I knew it.
I told you I'm heading to the farm.
Just have one bite. Just one.
Thank you for the food.
I guess you like it.
Have those rocks in your heart
dislodged now?
You said I couldn't stop it
from happening anyway.
Are you giving her the mushrooms?
I think Ms. Dam
is someone I can trust.
Right.
Were you with sweetie last night?
What?
I didn't see your car around this morning.
I slept at the office.
And stop trying to put
Ms. Dam and I together.
I've treated you to a meal,
so you'd better give me
a wedding invitation soon.
Ma'am!
Here, drink some water.
FINALLY IN KOREA
IN 9 DAYS
A SINGLE MIRACULOUS DROP,
AMAZING SKIN TRANSFORMATION
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
L'ÉTOILE LA FIN ESSENCE
Everything's great about this essence,
except for this.
There are some complaints about the pump.
It leaks often,
and many reviews say the suction is weak,
so it won't work at all
once it's about half used.
To be honest,
I also switched it with a different pump
that fits the bottle.
I think this is a pretty important issue.
What do you think?
You're not asking us
to switch the pumps, are you?
Will it be possible?
The pumps were made using a custom mold
that reflects L'Étoile's identity.
Does L'Étoile prioritize its identity
over customer convenience?
Hang on.
What?
This isn't a one-time thing.
So it's all okay
just because it's L'Étoile?
Just hang on.
So, Mr. Seo…
Did you see the ads they put up
in the building on the way here?
Yes.
Then, you must have seen
my name in large font on them too.
I did.
Now that I have my name on it,
disappointing customers
with L'Étoile products
will be a blow to my pride.
If you just switch the pumps,
I really think I can introduce this
to everyone with confidence.
We'll switch them.
So please introduce it
as the perfect essence.
Thank you so much, Mr. Seo.
Where did you go
in such a hurry last night?
I had something to do.
At that late hour?
By any chance,
did you get any calls
from an unknown number?
I always get calls from unknown numbers.
From Jamie in the US,
from Mr. Kim guaranteeing high returns…
Don't even get me started.
Ms. Dam will contact you as well.
I left her your number.
Why?
Did Ms. Dam ask for my number?
Did her network say
-they needed my help?
-No.
Something came up,
so we have to communicate through you
for about ten days
until the broadcast ends.
Please tell me when she contacts you.
Fine.
Sorry for not telling you in advance.
I'd appreciate the help.
Well, you never tell me anything
in advance or apologize anyway…
Mr. Park, aren't you going to work?
There's only one shovel.
We can't offer a discount,
so we'll have to focus
on brand power this time.
We can still emphasize that it's 15%
cheaper than ordering from overseas.
-That's important.
-It is.
Where did we put our list
of key selling points?
My coffee tastes like essence.
Let's have some snacks first
before continuing.
As I said before,
we're going to have to communicate
and follow up with the PR team
to promote the broadcast.
WELCOME TO HIT HOMESHOPPING, L'ÉTOILE
Do we have anything left on our agenda?
Having delicious desserts?
I'm sure you didn't return
just to give us desserts.
What brings you here?
I came to see you.
I can't even joke around.
I brought some news.
I just met with our packaging supplier.
We decided to start off
with 10,000 bottles for the launch at HIT.
That's actually great news.
Then, I'll be selling L'Étoile's
first-ever limited-edition essence.
Would you ever consider
working for L'Étoile?
You'd better get in line.
Take it. I still have
some work left to do.
Michelle?
My gosh. You really have no shame, do you?
I send you a gift,
and you don't even give me a single call?
If you knew what I gave up
to answer your call,
you wouldn't be able to say that.
Is the Korean launch coming along well?
Yes.
Don't worry.
Yes?
Can we talk for a moment?
Are you really going
to launch L'Étoile's essence?
You really are doing it.
By the way you're reacting,
I guess I'm pretty good at what I do.
Quit this right now.
Why should I listen to you?
Ruining my life was enough,
don't you think?
Just because I returned to HIT
doesn't mean that what happened
five years ago is all in the past.
Do you really not know
why I wanted
to do that broadcast?
How can you be so shameless?
You were desperate to debut.
Who are you trying to blame?
Everyone is saying
that you're not
the same Dam Ye-jin as before.
But what are we going to do?
You're still the same in my eyes.
Thanks for the advice.
You just made me
really eager to do well this time.
Ms. Dam wants to meet you
at Seoul Municipal Library at 9:00 p.m.
SHE PAINTS HER PICTURE WITHIN MINE
COSMETIC MICROBIOLOGY
Did you block my number, by any chance?
What?
MR. MECHOORI, 2 OUTGOING CALLS
Why weren't you picking up?
I didn't know you called.
Thank you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Come on…
COSMETIC MICROBIOLOGY
You didn't have to help me this much.
But are you sure
you can read all this
before the broadcast?
You'll barely have time
to learn your script.
My script?
Have you ever seen a Taekwondo athlete
fight during a competition
by doing all the forms in order?
Every second is a battle.
There's no script.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
I forgot to have dinner.
This is an emergency.
Are you on the run from someone?
Slow down.
It's a habit.
I have about ten meetings a day,
so I just eat food
as if I'm putting in fuel.
No one spends
more than ten minutes filling up.
You're done already?
Yes.
What's that look?
I'm just feeling glad I added
that special clause in the contract.
What do you mean by that?
"Seeing her act, I knew Dam Ye-jin
was full of risks." Is that it?
I didn't know you didn't use scripts.
I thought you were just reciting
what your clients gave you.
I only meant that I'm relieved
I got to learn more about you.
What did you think home shopping hosts do?
It's hard to do
an hour-long show without a script.
I'm sure everyone else will be amazed too.
Then,
should I tell you what my secret is?
You just have to love the products.
If you love them, you just want
to keep talking about them.
What? Do I seem cool?
Just finish your food.
Do you know how hard farmers had to work
to produce the lettuce and tomatoes
in that sandwich?
Fine.
I feel much better now.
You just have to love the products.
If you love them, you just want
to keep talking about them.
Guys.
I got a 97.6%
on the skin barrier improvement test.
I must be a genius.
You can't achieve that
just by using expensive ingredients.
You know that, right?
Come on, it's 97.6%!
Mr. Lee.
This is our storyboard for the shoot.
I thought it'd be nice
if you took a look before the shoot.
I notified you before,
but please be careful when moving around,
especially with your equipment.
Of course.
Don't touch any of the mushrooms directly.
And access to the area
with the original specimen is limited.
Please make sure not to harm
any mushrooms while filming.
Of course, sir.
I'll make sure
to instruct our crew clearly.
Thank you so much
for agreeing to the shoot.
-Ms. Dam.
-Yes?
Here's the final outline.
Sure.
-We marked the revised parts.
-Sorry. Hang on.
Did you forget something?
-I'll hold that.
-Thanks.
I think these will feel
and suit the vibe better today.
They seem to suit our concept better too.
Ms. Dam.
Mr. Seo.
Did you get some sleep?
I couldn't sleep a wink.
Were you nervous?
I told you it's nothing special.
The PR team made a request,
-so let me take your photos.
-Sure.
They say it's for a promotional article
to celebrate the launch in Korea.
Good. Smile.
Stand a little closer.
Good! Amazing! Good!
Awesome.
Très bien!
"Très bien"?
Good, good! Excellent!
Is there anything bothering you?
-Mr. Lee?
-Yes?
No.
It seems like there is.
How are they?
These don't belong
in the business section.
They should be
in the entertainment section!
They look great.
I'm sorry.
Did you have breakfast?
Yes. What about you?
I did too.
You weren't too nervous to eat, were you?
A little bit…
Nice to see you again.
Right.
We meet again.
Just think of this as giving Ms. Dam
a tour of this raw material farm.
No need to be nervous. Just act natural.
Keep introducing the farm
as you slowly walk on.
Good luck!
Let's go, Mr. Seo.
Okay, ready! Action.
-This way, please.
-All right.
Hey, Mechoori.
Don't be nervous.
The camera's faced that way.
The camera angle.
It's not like that.
Don't be silly.
I can tell you're totally scared.
Be careful.
They can still pick up your voice.
Geez.
Okay, your voices
won't be recorded this time.
So just follow the directions I give you.
To the workers in the back,
you can just keep working as normal.
Don't look at the camera
until I say "cut." Keep that in mind.
You two do a handshake first.
No, let's try that again.
You suddenly look so distant.
Give each other a friendly gaze.
Then, shake hands.
How about a bright smile?
Brighter.
Mr. Seo.
Hold on. What's that?
Cut!
Mr. Lee!
Mr. Lee?
Yes?
Don't look at the camera.
You were staring.
Just keep working, Mr. Lee.
What was that? Let's go again.
Mechoori.
The camera's faced this way.
You shouldn't hide though.
Be in the background of the picture.
And by "picture,"
I don't mean like a painting.
All right, I get it.
Okay, Mr. Lee. You just have to harvest
the mushrooms like you always do.
I'll give you some directions as we go.
-Okay.
-Okay?
Let's go.
Ready!
Action.
That was neat. He's good.
Good. Mr. Lee,
how about brushing it off a bit?
All right.
Gosh, we can see the craftsmanship
in those brush strokes.
-There you go.
-That's great, Mr. Lee.
How about harvesting a mushroom up top?
Ms. Dam, what are you doing after this?
This evening?
I have to wrap up and…
Is he crazy?
Those are expensive mushrooms.
What was that?
Did I tell him to crush it?
-No, you didn't.
-I said to harvest it.
No, I just…
Mechoori.
Your face is too frozen.
The camera's just going to
film your hand--
It's not because of the camera!
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's not because of the camera! It's not!
I told you I didn't want to do this.
Just because you do NeoTube…
I know what camera angles are.
I know! I know, okay?
Cut! Why don't we take a short break?
-Hey, go settle things down.
-Yes, let's take a short break.
Just for a moment.
Have some drinks, everyone.
-I brought these sweets.
-There's coffee.
It's coffee. This is amazing.
-Thank you, Mr. Seo.
-You're the best, Mr. Seo.
Thank you for the coffee.
-This is expensive stuff.
-Gosh, this is the good kind.
Thank you, sir.
Gojeuneok Bio is buying!
What's that?
Gosh, the chocolate one looks good.
DRINKS ARE ON GOJEUNEOK BIO!
Sir?
But…
Here's your Mechoori iced tea.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-What did you order?
-Unnie's Power.
In that case,
I'd like a Real Jolly Pongpong.
-Those two.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COOPERATION
Thanks for the drinks.
Thank you for this.
-It'll be ready soon, so please wait.
-Okay.
It's Ae-ra.
-One wild dog.
-What wild dog?
-Right behind me.
-Where? Behind you?
Ae-ra's here!
Hello. What would you like?
This is my territory.
I see. I'm sorry, but what is this about?
Right. You should be sorry.
Around here,
everyone drinks only Moon Cafe coffee.
But I stopped work and rushed over
when I heard about this!
I see. I'm a part of this farm's staff.
We have an important shoot today,
so I prepared--
I get it.
So you didn't want coffee
from some country girl
on your important day?
No, it's not that.
This is why I don't talk
to people from Seoul.
You're a bunch of thieves.
I don't think you need to worry.
You'll have many customers
with that kind of beauty.
DEOKPUNG COMMUNITY CENTER
Goodness, good work today!
Hey, Mechoori.
There's a lot of delicious food.
Sit down.
-Ms. Yang.
-Hey, sweetie.
Darling, the food's going to get cold.
Hurry up and sit.
Here. Sit down. Right there.
There's a lot of delicious food!
Mr. Seo, this way.
Move over! What is all this?
-Cockles!
-There's a ton!
-This looks good!
-How did they get these?
Have you tried this before?
It'll be my first time!
What is this? This is insane.
I haven't seen this in a while.
What is all this?
DON'T THOSE TWO LOOK BETTER TOGETHER?
YOU'RE CLUELESS, JONG-IL
THOSE TWO LOOK BETTER TOGETHER
DON'T BE SILLY!
SOMEONE FROM ABROAD
WOULD SUIT MS. DAM BETTER!
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOU CAN'T EVEN SPEAK ENGLISH
GOING BY THEIR LOOKS,
THEY'RE A BETTER MATCH
MR. SEO'S RICH!
AND HE'S A HANDSOME MATCH TOO
CAN YOU HEAR US?
SURE, I CAN
AMAZING
YOU'RE ONE OF US
WHATEVER, I'M WITH FRANCE!
FRANCE IS THE BEST!
YOU HAVE NO LOYALTY
I'M WITH MECHOORI, NO MATTER WHAT!
GEEZ, YOU'RE UNBELIEVABLE
How about a bet then? I'm with France.
Fine, let's do it. I'm with Mechoori.
-It's France!
-It's Mechoori!
-France!
-Mechoori!
Is the food not good?
You're so busy talking.
-It's nothing. Let's eat.
-It's not that.
-Eat up.
-It looks so good.
Thank you for the food.
Oh, dear.
Ooh la la.
Gosh. What should I do?
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm sure this will be okay for you to eat.
It's fine. You won't have
much to eat on your side then.
There's a lot. Eat up.
Are you okay?
-Goodness!
-Gosh, they must be having a blast!
-What a scene!
-Hey, cheers!
Excuse us. Hello.
This looks so delicious.
-Mind if I sit here?
-Thank you for the food.
Go ahead.
That table's pretty entertaining too.
Let's see what happens.
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
This soup's great.
It's nice and rich.
You should try this too, Ms. Moon.
The perilla leaves are…
Just give it to me. I'll eat it.
What the heck?
There aren't any left.
Here.
Have this.
You didn't get to try any.
-Eat.
-Right.
These other dishes are good too.
Gosh, Kwang-mo's cheeks are bright red!
Our Kwang-mo
must have finally found new love.
I guess so. My goodness.
Gosh, that's so nice to see.
Jung-muk!
Jung-muk.
Can you check my heart?
My heart…
should only be beating for Ae-ra.
It must be broken.
This doesn't make sense!
Why was it suddenly pounding?
Why?
HELP SAVE YOUR FRIEND, JUNG-MUK!
You did a great job today, Mr. Seo.
You did better than I thought.
It was pretty fun.
And I think it'll keep getting more fun.
I can't believe I'm actually saying
that work is going to be fun.
It's all thanks to you.
I wouldn't have experienced this sense
of achievement if it weren't for you.
The broadcast hasn't
even happened yet, Mr. Seo.
You must be tired.
You should head in and rest.
Well, I…
I'm going to do more research
on the growing conditions
and characteristics of the mushrooms.
Our customers are keen on such details.
I'm curious about such details as well.
-Hello?
-Mr. Seo.
It's almost time
for your video call with the chairman.
All right.
I have to go.
Give me a call if you need anything.
Sure.
What are you doing?
I wanted to help you.
Take off your gloves
and take this.
Thanks for letting us do the shoot here.
It must have been a difficult decision.
Yes, and today will be
the first and last shoot here.
Was it that uncomfortable for you?
Then, why did you say yes
instead of refusing?
It was because of you, Ms. Dam.
You keep pushing ahead until you succeed,
Ms. Dam.
Well…
When and where should we meet tomorrow?
You decide and tell me.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm going to be busy for a while.
Is it okay to meet in Seoul?
It doesn't matter.
We can meet in front of your house too.
You'd come all the way to my house?
Yes.
All right.
Then, I'll see you at my house
at 9:00 p.m. tomorrow.
I mean, in front of my house.
PREMIUM GRADE
GOJEUNEOK BIO
Would this be good enough?
So from now on, you'll make them
with these new pumps?
Just the ones launching in Korea for now.
If market response is good,
we'll formally propose
a design renewal to headquarters.
-The camera angle will be important here.
-Yes?
Here's the final package
that just passed the drop test!
-Come on!
-Okay! I haven't opened it yet.
Hey, they look so pretty.
We could just use these as decor.
I can't wait to do
the broadcast for these.
-This is awesome.
-The scent is nice too.
Great. There's no smell
of mushrooms at all.
Stop, Ye-jin.
-What?
-You're doing it again.
My goodness.
Our meticulous QA team,
our sharp Ms. Eom,
and even me, the smart merchandiser,
are all checking the product.
Why are you so worried?
I don't know.
Everything's perfect,
so it's making me even more anxious.
L'ÉTOILE E
AUGUST 9, NO. 4
Let's prepare inserts
for various skin types.
And for the before and after too.
Okay, bye.
Gosh, thanks for coming all the way here.
-I--
-Hey, Mr. Hwang.
Right. Hang on.
I'll get going.
The human application test results
on our display panel…
Thank you.
Mr. Mechoori.
I took a taxi today.
Thank you.
Could you put that in here?
ANTACID
My meds…
Goodness.
Thank you.
Is HIT the Ministry of Food
and Drug Safety or something?
Are you the FDA?
The broadcast is tomorrow.
How long are you going to
keep checking the numbers for?
This is really the last time.
I'll call you one last time tonight.
Geez!
Thank you.
CHAMOMILE TEA
COFFEE CANDY
ENERGY BOOSTER
Ms. Dam.
ENERGY GUM
Are you planning to not sleep forever?
Well, I…
You sure do exert your authority
in a very sweet way.
I'm protecting our best player.
Just wait until the broadcast is over…
Oh, right. I forgot to contact you.
Well,
I don't need my meds today.
I'm staying up all night.
Follow me.
To where?
Are you angry?
Mr. Mechoori, I wasn't staying up
these past few days.
Today is just an important day.
But you haven't told me where we're going.
What is this place?
It's near your house.
Right…
I didn't even know
there was a place like this.
Why aren't you going to sleep tonight?
I still have something to check.
I can't sleep even with my meds
if something's bothering me.
The broadcast is tomorrow.
Is there still more to check?
There's one thing left.
Me.
I'm sure you know the feeling.
You told me last time
that you keep working
until you've done enough.
But…
how do you know when you've done enough?
I'm sure you know that better than I do.
Me?
You know yourself the best.
And you…
have done well so far.
So believe in yourself tomorrow.
ADD CONTACTS
DAM YE-JIN
Dam Ye-jin, are you sure
you've done the best you can?
I'm not sure.
I have to keep going
until I find the answer.
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
L'ÉTOILE LA FIN ESSENCE
ONLY ON HIT
FULL-SCALE LAUNCH TODAY
I want to gift a necklace
so they can wear it for an important show.
What would be nice?
Since it's a gift,
wouldn't it be more meaningful
for you to select it yourself?
We're not that close yet.
Instead of my choice, could you pick one
that women would find pretty?
All right. Well, in my opinion…
How about this one?
This is the most popular item
in our shop these days.
L'ÉTOILE E
AUGUST 16, NO. 1
AUGUST 9, NO. 1
L'ÉTOILE E
AUGUST 9, NO. 2
Mu-won, I…
What? What's wrong?
What is it?
MICROBIAL TESTING AND EXPECTED RESULTS
I think this one looks nice and clean.
-Good.
-Okay.
-Then, I'll try this on.
I need to go to HIT.
Hey, what are you going to do
if you go to HIT?
The live broadcast is in an hour.
That's why I have to go and stop them.
In an hour, the essence
will be sold across the country.
Even if L'Étoile issues a full recall,
they won't be able
to retrieve all of them.
-Hae-seok, just calm down.
-Mu-won.
This could lead
to another case like Som-yi.
Go on.
I'll contact L'Étoile.
GOJEUNEOK BIO CEO KANG MU-WON
Hello?
Microbes were detected?
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
L'ÉTOILE LA FIN ESSENCE
STUDIO C
-Where's Studio C?
-It's on the 8th floor.
Wait… Hold on!
Excuse me.
Where's Dam Ye-jin's green room?
If you go down and turn right,
it'll be there.
Ms. Dam!
Mr. Mechoori?
Microbes were detected in the essence.
What?
No, that can't be.
I checked dozens of times.
These are the test results
from an hour ago.
It's 360 CFU per gram.
That's much lower than the MFDS limit.
I know there's no issue
if you look at the numbers now.
But…
Compare them
with the numbers from three days ago.
At this growth rate,
we can't even be sure about tomorrow.
We have to stop today's broadcast.
Ms. Dam, stand by.
Ms. Dam.
EXPECTED NUMBER
28TH DAY
Ms. Dam.
Are you
seriously going to sell…
a compromised product?
I promised to meet
our customers at this hour.
FIRST EVER LAUNCH IN KOREA
TODAY, AUGUST 16
-Who are you?
-What are you doing?
I need to speak briefly with Ms. Dam.
-We're live--
-It's urgent!
Dam Ye-jin!
Ms. Dam!
You can't do the broadcast!
You can't go in!
Please. Dam Ye-jin…
I just need one moment. Please.
She can't do the broadcast!
Ms. Dam!
Hello, I'm Dam Ye-jin.
I'd like to sincerely thank everyone
who has shown such great interest
in the launch
of L'Étoile's La Fin Essence.
But before we begin the broadcast,
I'd like to apologize.
On tonight's show,
we will not be selling the essence.
SOLD OUT ON YOU
Did she just blow a prime time slot
worth millions of won per minute?
So you're saying that host did this
without even discussing it with you?
Don't lay a hand on Dam Ye-jin.
It seems Dam Ye-jin's going to
end up taking all the blame.
"We sell value with sincerity."
I made the choice
to keep the promise that HIT made.
Effective today, HIT will be terminating
its contract with you.
Ms. Dam!
Mom.
Are you okay?
Mechoori…
Come with me. Please.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park